roanoke.edu 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy | Roanoke College

**Privacy Policy Statement**

The following information explains the Internet Privacy Policy which Roanoke College has adopted for its website (http:www.roanoke.edu). The following is intended to explain our current internet privacy practices but shall not be construed as a contractual promise. We reserve the right to amend our Internet Privacy Policy and Internet Privacy Policy Statement at any time without notice.

 **Concerns**  
Please contact us with any concerns or questions via email at [webadmin@roanoke.edu](mailto:webadmin@roanoke.edu) or through the mail. Web Administrator  
221 College Lane  
Salem, VA 24153-3794

**Information Collected**

Our servers automatically collect information about your web browser, proxy or firewall servers and other relevant information about your browsing server on our site. Please be aware that none of this information can be used by anyone to identify you.

**Personal Information**

In the course of using this website, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us electronic mail (through a mailer or a Web form) to request information, you may sign up for a mailing list, you may personalize the site or you may send us your address so we may send you materials. Any personally identifiable information you send to us will be used only for the purpose indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff for response and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests. We will not sell, exchange or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required by law. We do not retain the information longer than necessary for normal operations. If you do not wish to have the information used in that manner, you are not required to provide it.

**Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information stored by your Web browser on behalf of a website. Portions of this site may use cookies to carry data about any session at the site from one web page to the next, and to provide customized content once you personalize the website. We do not forward cookies to any external parties. If you prefer not to grant us this right, consult the documentation provided with your Web browser to turn off the appropriate "accept cookies" feature in your browser. The settings on cookies contained in your browser constitute a grant of permission (or lack thereof) for us to store information on your computer. We follow all industry standards in constructing and storing cookies with your browser. Thus, it is your browser vendor's responsibility to provide for secure and appropriate cookie storage mechanisms.

**Communications**

We reserve the right to contact you without prior notice through the use of email. We may, at times, send you marketing or promotional email messages regarding the College. If you request that your name be removed from the email list, we will discontinue the sending of bulk marketing and promotional email messages.

**External Links**

Our website may provide links to other websites or resources. We do not contact these sites and resources, we do not endorse them, and we are not responsible for their availability, content or delivery of services. In particular, external sites are not bound by the College's online privacy policy; they may have their own or none at all. Since we cannot guarantee the same level of privacy and security of these sites, we recommend that you read their privacy policies, which may differ from ours.
